Library of American Broadcasting Scripts collection
University of Maryland Libraries
1925-1991
1930-1960
Mass Media and Culture Special Collections, University of Maryland Libraries, Hornbake Library, College Park, MD 20742. Tel: 301-405-9212, Fax: 301-314-2709, Email: askhornbake@umd.edu
Library of American Broadcasting Scripts Collection
27.00 linear feet
2014-157
The Library of American Broadcasting Scripts Collection is a collection of radio and television scripts gathered from several sources and donations by the original staff of the Library of American Broadcasting. Dating from 1925 to 1991, these scripts are the actual scripts used by radio and television performers. Many of the scripts contain the hand-written markings the performers created as they were preparing the script for broadcast. These scripts document almost seventy years of radio and television broadcasting and represent a variety of genres, including comedy, drama, soap operas, quiz programs, news programs, and music programs.
Important Information for Users of the Collection
Use and Access to Collection
There are no restricted files in this collection.
Custodial History and Acquisition Information
The Library of American Broadcasting Script Collection came to the University of Maryland in 1994 as part of the Broadcast Pioneers Library
Administrative History
The Library of American Broadcasting was established as the Broadcast Pioneers Library (BPL) by the Broadcast Pioneers Educational Fund, Inc., now the Library of American Broadcasting Foundation, Inc, to preserve the history of radio and television broadcasting. The BPL/LAB accomplished this goal by collecting books, magazines, photographs, personal papers, audio recordings, film and video records, and, of course, radio and television scripts. The BPL was dedicated on April 19, 1972 and was originally located on the ground floor of the headquarters building of the National Association of Broadcasters in Washington, DC. In 1994, The BPEF moved the BPL to the University of Maryland to join the National Public Broadcasting Archives, which was already in place.
Scope and Content of Collection
The Library of American Broadcast Script Collection represents all forms of radio and television programming from 1925 to 1991, including drama, comedy, music, and news programming.
The collection is arranged alphabetically by program title and by date if more than one episode of a program is present. Due to this simple arrangement, the collection is arranged into only one series: Radio and Television Scripts.
Series 1: Radio and television Scripts
Related Material
The Library of American Broadcasting Script Collection is one of several collections of scripts to be found within the Special Collections in Mass Media and Culture. Scripts can also be found as parts of personal papers collections documenting the work of specific men and women involved in broadcasting.
For other related archival and manuscript collections, please see the following
subject guides
.
Bibliography
Brooks, Tim and Earle Marsh. The Complete Directory to Prime Time Network and Cable TV Shows, 1946-Present. New York, NY: Ballantine Books, 1999. Dunning, John. On the Air: The Encyclopedia of Old Time Radio. New York, NY: Oxford University Press, 1998. Poteet, G. Howard. Published Radio, Television, and Film Scripts; A Bibliography. Troy, NY: Whitston Pub. Co, 1975. Siegel, Susan. Radio Scripts in Print: Books Featuring 1,700 Golden Age of Radio Scripts. Yorktown Heights, NY: Book Hunter Press, 2006.
Selected Search Terms
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the University of Maryland Libraries' Catalog. Researchers desiring related materials about these topics, names, or places may search the Catalog using these headings.
Contents of Collection
- Radio and television Scripts, 1925-1991; 723 items
  A collection of original radio and television scripts dating from 1925 to 1991. These scripts represent all forms of radio and television programming, including drama, comedy, quiz programs, music programs, and news programs.
- Radio and television Scripts, 1925-1991; 723 items
  - ABC News Special -- National Polling Day: What Americans Think, 1/13/1971 (Box 1, Folder 1.0)
    - ABC News Special, 1/13/1971 (Item null)
  - Accidents Are Not Safety, 10/21/1943 (Folder 2.0)
    - Accidents Are Not Safety, 10/21/1943 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- An Ingenue of the Sierras, 1/10/1949 (Folder 3.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 1/10/1949 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- The Midway, 12/13/1949 (Folder 4.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 12/13/1949 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- Country Full of Swedes, 12/27/1949 (Folder 5.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 12/27/1949 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- Hannah, 1/3/1950 (Folder 6.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 1/3/1950 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- The Little Wife, 1/17/1950 (Folder 7.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 1/17/1950 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- The Timid Guy, 1/24/1950 (Folder 8.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 1/24/1950 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- Joe McSeen's Atomic Machine, 1/31/1950 (Folder 9.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 1/31/1950 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- The King, 2/3/1950 (Folder 10.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 2/3/1950 (Item null)
  - Actor's Studio, The -- A Frame Up, 11/14/1950 (Folder 11.0)
    - Actor's Studio, The, 11/14/1950 (Item null)
  - Adventures of Father Brown, The -- Arrows of Heaven, The, 6/17/1945 (Folder 12.0)
    - Adventures of Father Brown, The, 6/17/1945 (Item null)
  - Alcoholism: Out of the Shadows, 6/23/1971 (Folder 13.0)
    - Alcoholism: Out of the Shadows, 6/23/1971 (Item null)
  - Alka-Seltzer Barn Dance, 6/11/1938 (Folder 14.0)
    - Alka-Seltzer Barn Dance, 6/11/1938 (Item null)
  - All Star Game Opening, 8/31/1938 (Folder 15.0)
    - All Star Game Opening, 8/31/1938 (Item null)
  - All Things Considered, 4/18/1991 (Folder 16.0)
    - All Things Considered, 4/18/1991 (Item null)
  - America in the Air -- Skyways of Tommorrow, 2/27/1944 (Folder 17.0)
    - America in the Air, 2/27/1944 (Item null)
  - America in the Air -- France is Free to Speek, 10/7/1944 (Folder 18.0)
    - America in the Air, 10/7/1944 (Item null)
  - American Authors and What They -- Tom Paine... A True Revelation, 10/8/1946 (Folder 19.0)
    - American Authors and What They, 10/8/1946 (Item null)
  - American Authors and What They -- Herman Melville - "Moby Dick and Others, 10/15/1946 (Folder 20.0)
    - American Authors and What They, 10/15/1946 (Item null)
  - American Authors and What They -- Oliver Wendell Holmes, 11/12/1946 (Folder 21.0)
    - American Authors and What They, 11/12/1946 (Item null)
  - American Authors and What They -- James Fenimore Cooper, 11/19/1946 (Folder 22.0)
    - American Authors and What They, 11/19/1946 (Item null)
  - American Authors and What They -- Harriet Beecher Stowe, 12/10/1946 (Folder 23.0)
    - American Authors and What They, 12/10/1946 (Item null)
  - Amos 'n' Andy -- East, Central & West, 4/27/1936 (Folder 24.0)
    - Amos 'n' Andy, 4/27/1936 (Item null)
  - Anacin Hollywood Star Theatre, 9/24/1949 (Folder 25.0)
    - Anacin Hollywood Star Theatre, 9/24/1949 (Item null)
  - Armstrong's Theatre of Today -- Not to Love the Moonlight, 3/24/1945 (Folder 26.0)
    - Armstrong's Theatre of Today, 3/24/1945 (Item null)
  - Army Hour, The, 12/24/1944 (Folder 27.0)
    - Army Hour, The, 12/24/1944 (Item null)
  - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/4/1938 (Folder 28.0)
    - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/4/1938 (Item null)
  - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/7/1938 (Folder 29.0)
    - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/7/1938 (Item null)
  - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/11/1938 (Folder 30.0)
    - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/21/1938 (Folder 31.0)
    - Arnold Grimm's Daughter, 7/21/1938 (Item null)
  - Attorney at Law -- Case of the Asia Express, The, 7/5/1938 (Folder 32.0)
    - Attorney at Law, 7/5/1938 (Item null)
  - Attorney at Law -- Murder in Surgery, 7/12/1938 (Folder 33.0)
    - Attorney at Law, 7/12/1938 (Item null)
  - Attorney at Law -- Case of the Russian Wolf, The, 7/19/1938 (Folder 34.0)
    - Attorney at Law, 7/19/1938 (Item null)
  - Aunt Fanny and Grampa Putterball, 7/5/1938 (Folder 35.0)
    - Aunt Fanny and Grampa Putterball, 7/5/1938 (Item null)
  - Aunt Fanny and Grampa Putterball, 7/26/1938 (Folder 36.0)
    - Aunt Fanny and Grampa Putterball, 7/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Avalon Time, 7/1/1939 (Folder 37.0)
    - Avalon Time, 7/1/1939 (Item null)
  - Avalon Time, 8/5/1939 (Folder 38.0)
    - Avalon Time, 8/5/1939 (Item null)
  - Avalon Time, 8/12/1939 (Folder 39.0)
    - Avalon Time, 8/12/1939 (Item null)
  - Avalon Time, 8/19/1939 (Folder 40.0)
    - Avalon Time, 8/19/1939 (Item null)
  - Avalon Time, 4/17/1940 (Folder 41.0)
    - Avalon Time, 4/17/1940 (Item null)
  - Avalon Time, 4/24/1940 (Folder 42.0)
    - Avalon Time, 4/24/1940 (Item null)
  - Avalon Time, 5/1/1940 (Folder 43.0)
    - Avalon Time, 5/1/1940 (Item null)
  - Backstage Wife, 7/8/1938 (Folder 44.0)
    - Backstage Wife, 7/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Backstage Wife, 7/12/1938 (Folder 45.0)
    - Backstage Wife, 7/12/1938 (Item null)
  - Backstage Wife, 7/22/1938 (Folder 46.0)
    - Backstage Wife, 7/22/1938 (Item null)
  - Bald Knob Easter Sunrise Service, 3/16/1946 (Folder 47.0)
    - Bald Knob Easter Sunrise Service, 3/16/1946 (Item null)
  - Ballad of Gulf Curve, The, 1/1/1942 (Folder 48.0)
    - Ballad of Gulf Curve, The, 1/1/1942 (Item null)
  - Barber Bill - Audition, 12/7/1946 (Folder 49.0)
    - Barber Bill - Audition, 12/7/1946 (Item null)
  - Believe it or Not with Bob Ripley, 5/31/1940 (Folder 50.0)
    - Believe it or Not with Bob Ripley, 5/31/1940 (Item null)
  - Better Way, A, 3/9/1949 (Folder 51.0)
    - Better Way, A, 3/9/1949 (Item null)
  - Big Sister, 9/16/1936 (Folder 52.0)
    - Big Sister, 9/16/1936 (Item null)
  - Blue Ribbon Town -- Milwaukee, 2/5/1944 (Folder 53.0)
    - Blue Ribbon Town, 2/5/1944 (Item null)
  - Blue Ribbon Town -- Peoria - Preview, 2/10/1944 (Folder 54.0)
    - Blue Ribbon Town, 2/10/1944 (Item null)
  - Blue Ribbon Town -- Peoria, 2/12/1944 (Folder 55.0)
    - Blue Ribbon Town, 2/12/1944 (Item null)
  - Bob Hope Show, The, 1/1/1941 (Folder 56.0)
    - Bob Hope Show, The, 1/1/1941 (Item null)
  - Book Box, The -- Carnival Time at Strobeck, 4/1/1947 (Folder 57.0)
    - Book Box, The, 4/1/1947 (Item null)
  - Book Box, The -- Bhimsa the Dancing Bear, 4/15/1947 (Folder 58.0)
    - Book Box, The, 4/15/1947 (Item null)
  - Buttram-Murphy Routine, 5/18/1946 (Folder 59.0)
    - Buttram-Murphy Routine, 5/18/1946 (Item null)
  - Buttram-Murphy Routine, 5/25/1946 (Folder 60.0)
    - Buttram-Murphy Routine, 5/25/1946 (Item null)
  - Buttram-Murphy Routine, 6/1/1946 (Folder 61.0)
    - Buttram-Murphy Routine, 6/1/1946 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/6/1941 (Folder 62.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/6/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/13/1941 (Folder 63.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/13/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/20/1941 (Folder 64.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/20/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/27/1941 (Folder 65.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/27/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/3/1941 (Folder 66.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/3/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/10/1941 (Folder 67.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/10/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/17/1941 (Folder 68.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/17/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/24/1941 (Folder 69.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/24/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/31/1941 (Folder 70.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/31/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/7/1941 (Folder 71.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/7/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/9/1941 (Folder 72.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/9/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/14/1941 (Folder 73.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/14/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/21/1941 (Folder 74.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/21/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/28/1941 (Folder 75.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 9/28/1941 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 2/18/1942 (Folder 76.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 2/18/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 2/25/1942 (Folder 77.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 2/25/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/4/1942 (Folder 78.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/4/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/11/1942 (Folder 79.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/11/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/18/1942 (Folder 80.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/18/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/25/1942 (Folder 81.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 3/25/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/1/1942 (Folder 82.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/1/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/8/1942 (Folder 83.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/8/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/15/1942 (Folder 84.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/15/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/22/1942 (Folder 85.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/22/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/29/1942 (Folder 86.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 4/29/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/6/1942 (Folder 87.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/6/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/13/1942 (Folder 88.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/13/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/20/1942 (Folder 89.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/20/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/27/1942 (Folder 90.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 5/27/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/3/1942 (Folder 91.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/3/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/10/1942 (Folder 92.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/10/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/17/1942 (Folder 93.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/17/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/24/1942 (Folder 94.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/24/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/30/1942 (Folder 95.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 6/30/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/14/1942 (Folder 96.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/14/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/21/1942 (Folder 97.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/21/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/28/1942 (Folder 98.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 7/28/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/4/1942 (Folder 99.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/4/1942 (Item null)
  - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/18/1942 (Folder 100.0)
    - Cab Calloway's Quizzicale, 8/18/1942 (Item null)
  - Cabin B-13 (Folder 101.0)
    - Cabin B-13, null (Item null)
  - Car Card Carnival, 7/3/1938 (Folder 102.0)
    - Car Card Carnival, 7/3/1938 (Item null)
  - Car Card Carnival, 7/10/1938 (Folder 103.0)
    - Car Card Carnival, 7/10/1938 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 6/1/1929 (Folder 104.0)
    - Cavalcade, 6/1/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 6/8/1929 (Folder 105.0)
    - Cavalcade, 6/8/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 6/20/1929 (Folder 106.0)
    - Cavalcade, 6/20/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 6/22/1929 (Folder 107.0)
    - Cavalcade, 6/22/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 6/29/1929 (Folder 108.0)
    - Cavalcade, 6/29/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 7/6/1929 (Folder 109.0)
    - Cavalcade, 7/6/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 7/13/1929 (Folder 110.0)
    - Cavalcade, 7/13/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 7/27/1929 (Folder 111.0)
    - Cavalcade, 7/27/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 8/3/1929 (Folder 112.0)
    - Cavalcade, 8/3/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 8/10/1929 (Folder 113.0)
    - Cavalcade, 8/10/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 8/17/1929 (Folder 114.0)
    - Cavalcade, 8/17/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 8/24/1929 (Folder 115.0)
    - Cavalcade, 8/24/1929 (Item null)
  - Cavalcade, 8/31/1929 (Folder 116.0)
    - Cavalcade, 8/31/1929 (Item null)
  - CBS Announcer Audition, 1/1/1943 (Folder 117.0)
    - CBS Announcer Audition, 1/1/1943 (Item null)
  - CBS News Radio Analysis, 1/1/1957 (Folder 118.0)
    - CBS News Radio Analysis, 1/1/1957 (Item null)
  - Charlie McCarthy Show, The -- Chicago Cut-in-for Award Live, 4/23/1939 (Folder 119.0)
    - Charlie McCarthy Show, The, 4/23/1939 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 10/12/1955 (Folder 120.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 10/12/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 10/19/1955 (Folder 121.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 10/19/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 10/26/1955 (Folder 122.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 10/26/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/2/1955 (Folder 123.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/2/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/9/1955 (Folder 124.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/9/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/16/1955 (Folder 125.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/16/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/23/1955 (Folder 126.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/23/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/30/1955 (Folder 127.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 11/30/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 12/7/1955 (Folder 128.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 12/7/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 12/14/1955 (Folder 129.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 12/14/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 12/21/1955 (Folder 130.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 12/21/1955 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/4/1956 (Folder 131.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/4/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/11/1956 (Folder 132.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/11/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/18/1956 (Folder 133.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/18/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/25/1956 (Folder 134.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1/25/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2/1/1956 (Folder 135.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2/1/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2/8/1956 (Folder 136.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2/8/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2/22/1956 (Folder 137.0)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2/26/1956 (Box 2, Folder 1.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2/26/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 3/7/1956 (Folder 2.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 3/7/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 3/14/1956 (Folder 3.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 3/14/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 3/21/1956 (Folder 4.0)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 3/21/1956 (Item null)
  - Chicago, Germany, 6/7/1942 (Folder 5.0)
    - Chicago, Germany, 6/7/1942 (Item null)
  - Church of the Air, 10/27/1940 (Folder 6.0)
    - Church of the Air, 10/27/1940 (Item null)
  - Church of the Air, 4/20/1941 (Folder 7.0)
    - Church of the Air, 4/20/1941 (Item null)
  - Church of the Air, 8/24/1941 (Folder 8.0)
    - Church of the Air, 8/24/1941 (Item null)
  - Clear and Present Danger: A Study of Loyalty in America, 6/5/1950 (Folder 9.0)
    - Clear and Present Danger: A Study of Loyalty in America, 6/5/1950 (Item null)
  - Club Matinee, 7/22/1938 (Folder 10.0)
    - Club Matinee, 7/22/1938 (Item null)
  - Club Matinee, 10/28/1938 (Folder 11.0)
    - Club Matinee, 10/28/1938 (Item null)
  - Conquest, 1/1/1957 (Folder 12.0)
    - Conquest, 1/1/1957 (Item null)
  - Contented Hour, 7/25/1938 (Folder 13.0)
    - Contented Hour, 7/25/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie Audition, 7/3/1936 (Folder 14.0)
    - Dale Carnegie Audition, 7/3/1936 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie Audition, 1/11/1938 (Folder 15.0)
    - Dale Carnegie Audition, 1/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie Hour, The, 1/1/1939 (Folder 16.0)
    - Dale Carnegie Hour, The, 1/1/1939 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Get Ahead, 1/1/1939 (Folder 17.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Get Ahead, 1/1/1939 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Get Ahead, 10/19/1939 (Folder 18.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Get Ahead, 10/19/1939 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win, 1/1/1939 (Folder 19.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win, 1/1/1939 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/23/1937 (Folder 20.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 7/23/1937 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/22/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 3/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/15/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 8/20/1937 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/8/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1/25/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/1/1938 (Item null)
    - Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, 2/8/1938 (Item null)